mirrorlesscomparison.com 2017-08-09

# Disclaimer, Privacy & Copyright Notice

## Disclaimer

The owner of this website, Heather Broster, is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking mirrorlesscomparison.com to Amazon properties including, but not limited to, amazon.com, amazon.co.uk, amazon.ca, amazon.it, endless.com, myhabit.com, smallparts.com, or amazonwireless.com.

Heather Broster and her partner Mathieu Gasquet are also a participants in the following affiliate programs: B&H Photo, eBay Partner Network, MacPhun, and Mediterranean Photo Tours.

## Privacy Policy for Mirrorless Comparison: http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at mirrorlessons@gmail.com.

At http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com does not use cookies.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense (more information [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/))
  * Google Analytics (more information [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/))
  * Mediavine
  * B&H Photo
  * Amazon (US, UK)
  * eBay Partner Network
  * MacPhun
  * Mediterranean Photo Tours

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.mirrorlesscomparison.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Ethic Statement

The content on this website is written and produced as an expression of our passion for mirrorless cameras and photography in general. We are not paid by any of the brands, camera manufacturers, lenses or accessories mentioned in our articles. We provide you with honest reviews and thoughts, which reflect our personal point of view.

## Copyright Notice

All content (brand, images, logos, videos and text) featuring the Mirrorless Comparison or MirrorLessons logo on this website are property of Mathieu Gasquet and Heather Broster, unless otherwise stated, and cannot be reproduced without the express permission of the owners.
